{"_id":{"$oid":"536a8c9bd3be723956c85634"},"answer":"False","lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1399646007485"},"question":"The sky is white.","type":"trueFalse","userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"views":2}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536a8ccaebff563b58faf338"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118155481e+12,"type":"multipleChoiceSingleAnswer","question":"","options":["1950","1948","1930","1984"],"answer":"1948"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536a8e3dd024ceba5ca61896"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118619345e+12,"type":"multipleChoices","question":"Which of the below are even numbers?","options":["5",{"label":"13"},{"label":"31"},{"label":"54","checked":true},{"label":"45"},{"label":"68","checked":true},{"label":"86","checked":true}],"answer":[],"helpText":"","language":"english","subject":"math","age":7}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536b399058903021362dd1ca"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118995976e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"The opposite of hot is ______  .","answer":"cold","options":[{"label":"cold","checked":true},{"label":"Cold","checked":true}],"language":"english","subject":"spelling","age":8}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536b90fc525245592da4d1af"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118350367e+12,"type":"trueFalse","question":"Birds can always fly.","answer":"False"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536b91b4dbac8bc731c4326b"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1400488675475"},"type":"trueFalse","question":"The number 2 is spelled as \"tow\".","answer":"False"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536cb021276c74002cd2d24f"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118779025e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"How do you spell the word 40?","options":["fourti",{"label":"forty","checked":true},{"label":"Forty","checked":true}],"answer":"forty","language":"english","subject":"spelling","age":8}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536cb8df7c77e72042bbc8d1"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404119045208e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"How do you spell the number 5?","answer":"[five, Five]","options":[{"label":"Five","checked":true},{"label":"five","checked":true}],"language":"english","subject":"spelling","age":6}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536cc9a1cccdf4585b24d390"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1399638509837"},"type":"trueFalse","question":"המספר 7 כתובים שבה","answer":"False"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536df871beb2119a597a7c37"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404112556758e+12,"type":"multipleChoices","question":"yes","options":[{"label":""},{"label":"לא"},{"label":"כן","checked":true},{"label":"מה"},{"label":"אני"}],"answer":"כן","helpText":"פירוש המילה הוא...","language":"hebrew","subject":"english","age":8}
{"_id":{"$oid":"536df8b4d0cdc0245b4c996d"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1403236305256"},"type":"multipleChoices","question":"no","options":[{"label":"מה"},{"label":"אני"},{"label":"לא","checked":true},{"label":"כן"}],"answer":[],"helpText":"פירוש המילה הוא...","language":"hebrew","subject":"english","age":8}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537093cec996420864b28759"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1400488252114"},"type":"trueFalse","question":"This sentence is spelled correctly:  \"This is there book, not mine.","answer":"False"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5371ee415a8f798b218ebeb8"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.40412629969e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"The number 7 is spelled _____","answer":"seven","options":[{"label":"Seven","checked":true},{"label":"seven","checked":true}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5371ee7c2f2ae3a9222652ff"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1400488359738"},"type":"trueFalse","question":"The following sentence is spelled correctly:  They're good kids.","answer":"True"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537265c6cfa94d9e421112bf"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404119083616e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"How do you spell the number 2?","answer":"[two, Two]","options":[{"label":"two","checked":true},{"label":"Two","checked":true}],"language":"english","subject":"spelling","age":6}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537265e4dbef168445d99d54"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118696825e+12,"type":"multipleChoices","question":"What is the capital of Israel?","options":[{"label":"Jerusalem","checked":true},{"label":"Tel Aviv"},{"label":"Pune"},{"label":"New York"}],"answer":"Jerusalem","language":"english","subject":"geography","age":8}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537341897413557651bcf832"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404118740441e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"מהו המספר העוקב ל– 6,000?","answer":"[6,001,\u00096001]","options":[{"label":"6,001","checked":true},{"label":"6001","checked":true}],"language":"hebrew","subject":"math","age":8}
{"_id":{"$oid":"53734310e443cf2e54746320"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.49366412315e+12,"type":"multipleChoices","question":"לפתור: _____ =  600 + 6,395","answer":"[6,895 , 6895]","options":[{"label":"6,995","checked":true},{"label":"12,095"},{"label":"6,455"},{"label":"7,005"}],"helpText":"בחר את הפתרון הנכון לתרגיל.","language":"hebrew","subject":"math","age":9}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537343a02ef0d37057db2897"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404119273457e+12,"type":"exactMatch","question":"Solve:   6,395+600 =  _____","answer":"[6,895,\u00096895]","options":[{"label":"6995","checked":true},{"label":"6,695","checked":true}],"language":"english","subject":"math","age":9}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5373524efce8fdab6d32a7de"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404119375777e+12,"type":"multipleChoices","question":"בקופסא של שקד היו 30 תותים. אחרי ששקד נתנה למיקה תותים מהקופסא, נשארו לה 13 תותים. כמה תותים נתנה שקד למיקה?","answer":[["17"]],"options":[{"label":"17 תותים","checked":true},{"label":"43 תותים"},{"label":"13 תותים"},{"label":"7 תותים"}],"language":"hebrew","subject":"math","age":9}
{"_id":{"$oid":"53737a257ec0e3a71ff5d56f"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1401055857279"},"type":"multipleChoicesMultipleAnswers","question":"Of the numbers below, which are even numbers?","options":["8","5","15","80","3","10","14","41","87"],"answer":["8","80","14","14","10","10","3","8","5","80","80"]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5373806446b044c32aa01beb"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1400149962374"},"type":"multipleChoicesMultipleAnswers","question":"Of the numbers below which are even numbers?","options":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7"],"answer":["2","4","1","5","3","1","5","6","6","7","4","3"]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"5373806d46b044c32aa01bec"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":1.404057857732e+12,"type":"trueFalse","question":"The word \"Their\" is a contraction of \"They are\".","answer":"False","language":"english"}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537497601a9c7b44033d1aaa"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1400149933959"},"type":"multipleChoicesMultipleAnswers","question":"Which are even numbers?","options":["3","1","2","4","5"],"answer":["3","2"]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"537497a75e9c591a068f90f8"},"userId":{"$oid":"53aec297f9fcc48f0cfe2f5a"},"lastUpdate":{"$numberLong":"1400150066488"},"type":"multipleChoicesMultipleAnswers","question":"Of the numbers below...","options":["1","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","9","10"],"answer":["2","4","6","8","10"]}
